His next target is now hunting him.
Survivor is a action, crime, mystery film directed by James McTeigue.
A Foreign Service Officer in London tries to prevent a terrorist attack set to hit New York,
but is forced to go on the run when she is framed for crimes she did not commit.
Kate Abbott, played by Milla Jovovich.
The Watchmaker, played by Pierce Brosnan.
Sam Parker, played by Dylan McDermott.
Maureen Cranepaul, played by Angela Bassett.
Bill Talbot, played by Robert Forster.
Paul Anderson, played by James D'Arcy.
Survivor is a 2015 action spy thriller film directed by
James McTeigue and written by Philip Shelby.
The film stars Milla Jovovich, Pierce Brosnan, Dylan McDermott, Robert Forster, Angela Bassett, Antonia Thomas,
James D'Arcy, Frances de la Tour, Genevieve O'Reilly, and - in his last ever film role - Roger Rees.
The film was released in cinemas in the United Kingdom on June 5, 2015,
and direct-to-video in the United States on June 23, 2015.
The film explores themes of new year's eve, new york
city, london, england, showdown, hostage.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.